NGUYEN QUOC KHANH

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

0948573111

Ha Dong, Hanoi

in Nguyen Quoc Khanh

nquockhanh0209v@gmail.com

02/09/2001

mguockhanh0209

ABOUT ME

A young person who is able to quickly learn and apply new technologies. Seeking the chance to bring further success to the organization's products through back-end performance.

Short term: Become a Back-end developer with languagues: Python, Nodejs and learn micro service from scratch in 3 months. **Long term:** Expert in not only software architechture but also system architechture in 5 years.

SKILLS

Back-end

- Database(SQL, NoSQL): Advance
- Python(Flask, Django, Selenium): Advance
- Nodejs(Nestjs, Expressjs): Advance
- Solidity: Advance
- AWS ec-2: Basic
- **Docker**: Intermediate
- Queue Service (RabbitMQ, Redis): Intermediate

Front-end

- Reactis (Nextis): Intermediate
- HTML/CSS: Basic

Soft skills

- Critical thinking
- Problem-solving
- English Written and Oral skills

WORK EXPERIENCE

Savvycom Software

R&D Intern • 6/2022- 12/2022

- Built a PoC HDWALLET app back-end to create several wallet addresses from a provided private key (Nodejs, MongoDB).
- Built a PoC NFT Marketplace: Back-end (Nodejs, MongoDB), Front-end (Reactjs), Smart contract (Solidity).
- Maintained a PoC Cross-Chain Bridge service and handling service error: Back-end (Nodejs, PostgresSQL, Redis)
- Wrote documents and created sequence diagrams for the above projects.

Graduation thesis

• 1/2023- 6/2023

Building a betting website using Blockchain token for betting and using Chainlink nodes for transferring real-world data to Smart contracts to handling.

- Wrote documents and created sequence diagram for the above projects.
- Built website: Back-end (Expressjs, MongoDB), Front-end (Reactjs).
- Customized and Run Chainlink node using Docker.
- Wrote the smart contracts for storing betting data (**Solidity**).
- Wrote units test for each function of the project

Grade 9.2/10.0.

MATA TECHNOLOGY SERVICES AND TRADING

Software Developer • 6/2023-Now

- Built NFT Marketplace:
 - Back-end (Nestjs, PostgresSQL):
 - Referral function.
 - Backup data to another database using a cron job.
 - Verify transactions: Buy, Mint NFTs and save to database.
 - Event functions: award the users who had bought and minted the number of NFTs in a week or a month.
 - Create API to create, read, update, delete NFTs and Buy NFTs.
 - Smart contract (Solidity):
 - Create contracts: NFT (ERC721), Token(ERC20).
 - Create contract buy NFT with Signature.
 - Implement upgradable contract.
 - Auction contract.

The website had been deployed to BSC Testnet. At least 100 users have joined this website, and nearly 500 NFTs minted in 2 months. This website has been also deployed to OpBNB Testnet and going to deploy to BSC Mainnet.

- Built Open Token Presale Platform:
 - Back-end (Nestjs, PostgresSQL):
 - Setup Database.
 - Backup data to another database using a cron job.
 - Verify transactions create tokens and presales.
 - Create API to create, read, update, delete tokens and presales.
 - Smart contract (**Solidity**):
 - Create contracts: Token(ERC20).
 - Create contract Presale and implement the upgradable contract.
 - Front-end (Nextis):
 - Create tokens and presales.
 - Display the presales information.
 - Checking time for start/end presale.
 - Checking if presales are available.
 - Handle call to smart contract functions: Buy token, Claim token, Refund token, End presale and auto add liquidity.

A tester had tested the website and is waiting for release.

- Built the service to get all the NFTs and NFTs attributes on-chain:
 - Back-end (Nestjs, MongoDB, RabbitMQ):
 - Handle crawl data from block 0 to current blocks for data of NFTs (ERC721 or ERC1155).
 - Handle get attributes of NFTs using RabbitMQ.
 - Classify the attributes of NFTs and send them to front-end or another service through RestAPI.

Service had run perfectly in BSC Testnet with at least 100k Nfts and NFTs attributes saved.

- Building tool for increasing impression to Twitter accounts and automation running the project accounts like a real human:
 - Back-end (Python, MongoDB, Selenium, RabbitMQ):
 - Divide into 2 back-end services: Order service for receive and publish orders to Bot service. Bot service consumes the
 messages received and runs bot to increase impressions for accounts in orders.
 - Using Selenium for emulation of the account action as a person.
 - Using Selenium to crawl data on Twitter to get data of service-ordered accounts.
 - Integrate ChatGpt and Google Bard to generate comments for Twitter posts.
 - Using RabbitMQ to publish messages from the Order server. Consume the messages in the Bot server.
 - Create API for reading data of new bot accounts from CSV file and save to database.

The project is running and receiving up to 800 orders in 7 days.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Vietnam National University • 2019-2023

CERTIFICATIONS

TOEIC Reading and Listening: 860

IIG Vietnam. • 2023